Guide to the Department of Athletics, Yale University, Motion Pictures Documenting Basketball
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
Department of Athletics, Yale University, motion pictures documenting basketball
1927-2003
RU 967
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
537
(1602 items)
The materials consist of motion picture films and videotapes documenting basketball at Yale.
Yale University. Dept. of Athletics
General note
Forms part of Yale Record Group 38-B (YRG 38-B), Records documenting specific sports at Yale.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
The materials were transferred from the Department of Athletics, 2004-2007 and 2015.
Conditions Governing Access
The materials are open for research.
Original audiovisual materials, as well as preservation and duplicating masters, may not be played. Researchers must consult use copies (designated by a 'U' suffix in the box number), or if none exist must pay for a use copy, which is retained by the repository. Researchers wishing to obtain an additional copy for their personal use should consult Copying Services information on the Manuscripts and Archives web site.
Copies of commercially produced audiovisual materials contained in this collection cannot be made for researcher use outside of the repository.
Arrangement
The materials are arranged by accession.
Scope and Contents
The materials consist of motion picture films and videotapes documenting basketball at Yale.
Basketball; College athletes; College sports; Motion pictures (visual works); Videotapes; Yale University -- Basketball; Yale University -- Sports; Yale University -- Students; Yale University. Dept. of Athletics
- Men's basketball game films, 1925-1959; Accession 2005-A-131
  - Holy Cross, 1925-1927 (Box 19)
  - Unknown Team, 1945-1946 (Box 20)
  - 1945-1948
    - Columbia, 1948 January 14; 4 (Box 1–4)
    - Cornell, 1948 January 17; 4 (Box 5–8)
    - Princeton, 1948 February 23; 2 (Box 9–10)
  - 1948-1949
    - Stanford, 1948 December 21; 2 (Box 11, Box 35)
    - NYU, 1948 December 26; 3 (Box 17–18, Box 47)
      - Use copy, videotape (VHS)
        General note
        See RU 971, ACCN 2006-A-031, Box 13
    - Penn, 1949; 2 (Box 165–166)
    - Army, 1949 January 28; film reel (16mm) (Box 12)
    - Princeton, 1949 February 5; film reel (16mm) (Box 13)
    - Dartmouth, 1949 February 16; 3 (Box 16, Box 160–161)
    - Holy Cross, 1949 February 19; 2 (Box 14–15)
    - Illinois (NCAA, 1st round), 1949; film reel (16mm) (Box 170)
    - Villanova (NCAA, consolation round), 1949; 3 (Box 162–164)
  - MISCELLANEOUS
    - Unknown team, Late 1940's - early 1950's; film reel (16mm) (Box 21)
    - Unknown team, 1940's late; film reel (16mm) (Box 22)
    - Unknown team, 1940's late; film reel (16mm) (Box 23)
    - Unknown team, 1950's early; 2 (Box 24–25)
    - Unknown team, 1950's early; 1 (Box 26)
    - Unknown team, 1950's early; film reel (16mm) (Box 27)
    - Unknown team, 1950's; 4 (Box 28–31)
    - Practice session (3 short clips), 1950's; film reel (16mm) (Box 32)
  - 1949-1950
    - NYU, 1949 December 29; 3 (Box 33–34, Box 48)
    - Dartmouth, 1950 January 18; 3 (Box 36–38)
    - Princeton, 1950 February 22; 3 (Box 39–41)
    - Harvard, 1950 March 11; film reel (16mm) (Box 42)
    - Harvard, 1950 March 4; film reel (16mm) (Box 43)
  - 1950-1951
    - NYU, 1950 December 19; 3 (Box 44–46)
    - Penn, 1950 December 9; 3 (Box 49–51)
    - Princeton, 1951 February 3; 3 (Box 52–54)
    - Harvard, 1951 March 3; film reel (16mm) (Box 55)
  - 1951-1952
    - Cornell, 1952; 3 (Box 56–58)
    - Dartmouth, 1952 February 12; film reel (16mm) (Box 59)
    - Columbia, 1952 February 26; 3 (Box 60–62)
    - Harvard, 1952 March 8; 3 (Box 63–65)
    - Penn, 1952 March 11; 3 (Box 66–68)
  - 1952-1953
    - Princeton, 1953 February 21; 3 (Box 69–71)
    - Dartmouth, 1953 February 7; 3 (Box 72–74)
    - Dartmouth, 1953 March 12; film reel (16mm) (Box 75)
  - 1953-1954
    - Dartmouth, 1954 January 6; 3 (Box 76–78)
    - Columbia, 1954 February 6; 3 (Box 79–81)
  - 1954-1955
    - Columbia, 1954 December 15; 3 (Box 82–84)
    - Penn, 1955 January 5; 3 (Box 85–87)
    - Cornell, 1955 January 14; 3 (Box 88–90)
    - Princeton, 1955 February 19; 3 (Box 91–93)
  - 1955-1956
    - UConn, 1955 December 7; 2 (Box 94–95)
    - Columbia, 1956 January 18; 3 (Box 96–98)
    - Penn, 1956 February 15; 3 (Box 99–101)
    - Princeton, 1956 February 22; 4 (Box 102–105)
    - Harvard, 1956 March; 2 (Box 106–107)
  - 1956-1957
    - Penn, 1956 December 14; 3 (Box 167–169)
    - Brown, 1957 January 9; 3 (Box 108–110)
    - Princeton, 1957 February 9; 3 (Box 111–113)
    - Cornell, 1957 February 16; 3 (Box 114–116)
    - Columbia, 1957 February 20; 4 (Box 117–120)
  - 1957-1958
    - UConn, 1957 December 7; film reel (16mm) (Box 121)
    - Penn, 1958 January 10; 4 (Box 122–125)
    - Princeton, 1958 January 11; 3 (Box 126–128)
    - Dartmouth, 1958 February 15; 3 (Box 129–130, Box 159)
    - Columbia, 1958 February 21; 3 (Box 131–133)
    - Cornell, 1958 February 22; 3 (Box 134–136)
    - Brown, 1958 February 12; 3 (Box 137–139)
  - 1958-1959
    - Dartmouth, 1959 January 6; 2 (Box 140–141)
    - Dartmouth (Reel 2/2), 1959 January 6 (Box 141)
    - Harvard, 1959 January 31; 2 (Box 142–143)
    - Princeton, 1959 February 7; 3 (Box 144–146)
    - Penn, 1959 February 8; 3 (Box 147–149)
    - Brown, 1959 February 11; 3 (Box 150–152)
    - Cornell, 1959 February 27; 3 (Box 153–155)
    - Columbia, 1959 February 28; 3 (Box 156–158)
- Men's basketball game films, 1959-1964; Accession 2005-A-136
  - 1959-1960
    - Fordham, 1959 December 9; 2 (Box 1–2)
    - Brown, 1959 December 16; 4 (Box 3–5, Box 94)
    - Princeton, 1960 January 8; 3 (Box 6–8)
    - Penn, 1960 January 9; 3 (Box 9–11)
      - Duplicating master for boxes 9-11, computer files (DVD-Video)
        Contact Public Services (phone: 203 432-1735, e-mail: mssa.reference@yale.edu) for information on accessing this digital object.
      - Use copy for boxes 9-11, optical disk (DVD) (Box 9U)
    - Cornell, 1960 February 19; 3 (Box 12–14)
    - Columbia, 1960 February 20; 3 (Box 15–17)
      Scope and Contents
      Notes on plays from reels 1 & 2 are in can
    - Dartmouth, 1960 March 4; 3 (Box 18–20)
      - Use copy for boxes 18-20, 1 (Box 18U)
    - Harvard, 1960 March 5; 3 (Box 21–23)
  - 1960-1961
    - Holy Cross, 1960 December 10; 2 (Box 24–25)
    - Brown, 1961 January 4; 3 (Box 95–97)
    - Dartmouth, 1961 January 7; 3 (Box 26–28)
    - Harvard, 1961 February 2; 3 (Box 29–31)
      - Use copy, 1 (Box 29U)
    - Penn, 1961 February 10; film reel (16mm) (Box 32)
      - Duplicating master, computer files (DVD-Video)
      - Use copy, optical disk (DVD) (Box 32U)
    - Princeton, 1961 February 11; 3 (Box 33–35)
    - Cornell, 1961 March 3; 3 (Box 36–38)
    - Columbia, 1961 March 4; 3 (Box 39–41)
  - 1961-1962
    - Fordham, 1961 December 6; 2 (Box 42–43)
    - Brown, 1962 January 6; 3 (Box 44–46)
    - Princeton, 1962 January 12; 3 (Box 47–49)
    - Cornell, 1962 February 16; 3 (Box 50–52)
    - Columbia, 1962 February 17; 3 (Box 53–55)
    - Dartmouth, 1962 March 2; 2 (Box 56–57)
  - 1962-1963
    - Holy Cross, 1962 December 8; 2 (Box 58–59)
    - Brown, 1963 January 5; 2 (Box 60–61)
    - Princeton, 1963 February 9; 3 (Box 62–64)
    - Cornell, 1963 February 15; 3 (Box 65–67)
    - Columbia, 1963 February 16; 3 (Box 68–70)
    - Dartmouth, 1963 March 1; 3 (Box 71–73)
  - 1963-1964
    - Holy Cross, 1963 December 14; film reel (16mm) (Box 74)
    - Dartmouth, 1964 January 31; 3 (Box 75–77)
    - Harvard, 1964 February 1; film reel (16mm) (Box 78)
    - Columbia, 1964 February 14; 3 (Box 79, Box 84–85)
    - Cornell, 1964 February 15; 4 (Box 80–83)
    - Princeton, 1964 February 21; 3 (Box 86–88)
    - Penn, 1964 February 22; 3 (Box 89–90, Box 98)
      - Duplicating master for boxes 89-90, 98", computer files (DVD-Video)
      - Use copy for boxes 89-90, 98", optical disk (DVD) (Box 89U)
    - Brown, 1964 March 4; 3 (Box 91–93)
- Men's basketball game films, 1964-1968; Accession 2005-A-161
  - 1964/1965
    - UConn, 1964 December 5; 3 (Box 1–3)
    - Brown, 1965 January 12; 3 (Box 4–6)
    - Penn, 1965 February 5; 3 (Box 7–9)
    - Princeton, 1965 February 6; 2 (Box 10–11)
    - Cornell, 1965 February 12; 3 (Box 12–14)
    - Columbia, 1965 February 13; 2 (Box 15–16)
    - Harvard, 1965 February 26; 3 (Box 17–19)
    - Dartmouth, 1965 February 27; 2 (Box 20–21)
  - 1965/1966
    - Fordham, 1965 December 8; 2 (Box 22–23)
    - Princeton, 1966 January 7; 2 (Box 24–25)
    - Penn, 1966 January 8; 4 (Box 26–29)
    - Columbia, 1966 February 4; 3 (Box 30–32)
    - Cornell, 1966 February 5; 3 (Box 33–35)
    - Dartmouth, 1966 February 18; 3 (Box 36–38)
    - Harvard, 1966 February 19; 3 (Box 39–41)
    - Brown, 1966 March 1; 2 (Box 42–43)
  - 1966/1967
    - UConn, 1966 December 3; 3 (Box 44–46)
    - Holy Cross, 1966 December 10; 2 (Box 47–48)
    - Brown, 1966 December 13; 3 (Box 49–51)
    - Cornell, 1966 December 16; 3 (Box 52–54)
    - Columbia, 1967 January 10; 4 (Box 55–58)
    - Harvard, 1967; 3 (Box 93–95)
    - Princeton, 1967 February 10; 4 (Box 59–62)
    - Penn, 1967 February 11; 3 (Box 63–65)
      - Duplicating master, computer files (DVD-Video)
      - Use copy for boxes 63-65, optical disk (DVD) (Box 63U)
    - Dartmouth, 1967 February 25; 2 (Box 66–67)
  - 1967/1968
    - Fordham, 1967 December 6; 3 (Box 68–69)
    - Brown, 1967 December 6; 2 (Box 70–71)
    - Dartmouth, 1968 February 2; 3 (Box 72–74)
    - Harvard, 1968 February 3; 3 (Box 75–77)
    - Penn, 1968 February 16; 4 (Box 78–81)
      - Duplicating master, computer files (DVD-Video)
      - Use copy for boxes 63-65", optical disk (DVD) (Box 78U)
    - Princeton, 1968 February 17; 3 (Box 82–84)
    - Cornell, 1968 February 23; 4 (Box 85–88)
    - Columbia, 1968 February 24; 4 (Box 89–92)
- Men's basketball game films, 1968-1972; Accession 2005-A-166
  - 1968-1969
    - UConn, 1968 November 30; 3 (Box 1–2, Box 95)
    - Brown, 1968 December 11; 3 (Box 3–5)
    - Columbia, 1969 January 10; 3 (Box 6–8)
    - Cornell, 1969 January 11; 3 (Box 9–11)
    - Princeton, 1969 February 14; 4 (Box 12–15)
    - Penn, 1969 February 15; 4 (Box 16–19)
      - Use copy for film reels 16-19, 1 (Box 16U)
    - Dartmouth, 1969 February 28; 4 (Box 20–23)
    - Harvard, 1969 March 1; 3 (Box 24–27)
  - 1969-1970
    - Brown, 1969 December 16; 3 (Box 28–30)
    - Cornell, undated; 3 (Box 92–94)
    - Harvard, 1970 January 30; 3 (Box 31–33)
    - Dartmouth, 1970 January 31; 3 (Box 34–36)
    - Columbia, 1970 February 7; 3 (Box 37–39)
    - Penn, 1970 February 20; 4 (Box 40–43)
    - Princeton, 1970 February 21; 3 (Box 44–45, Box 96)
  - 1970-1971
    - UConn, 1970 December 5; 3 (Box 46–48)
    - Brown, 1970 December 16; 3 (Box 49–51)
    - Columbia, 1971 January 8; 3 (Box 52–54)
    - Cornell, 1971 January 9; 3 (Box 55–57)
    - Princeton, 1971 February 12; 3 (Box 58–60)
    - Penn, 1971 February 13; 3 (Box 61–63)
    - Dartmouth, 1971 March 5; 3 (Box 64–66)
    - Harvard, 1971 March 6; 3 (Box 67–69)
  - 1971-1972
    - Brown, 1971 December 15; 4 (Box 70–73)
    - Cornell, 1972 January 7; 3 (Box 74–77)
    - Columbia, 1972 January 8; 2 (Box 78–79)
    - Harvard, 1972 February 11; 3 (Box 80–82)
    - Dartmouth, 1972 February 12; 3 (Box 83–85)
    - Penn, 1972 March 3; 3 (Box 86–88)
      - Use copy for film reels 86-88 (Box 86U)
    - Princeton, 1972 March 4; 3 (Box 89–91)
- Men's basketball game films, 1972-1977; Accession 2005-A-188
  - 1971-1972
    - Brown, 1972 December 19; 3 (Box 1–3)
  - 1972-1973
    - Columbia, 1973 January 5; 3 (Box 4–6)
    - Cornell, 1973 January 6; 3 (Box 7–9)
    - Dartmouth, 1973 February 16; 3 (Box 10–12)
    - Harvard, 1973 February 17; 3 (Box 13–15)
    - Princeton, 1973 February 23; 3 (Box 16–18)
    - Pennsylvania, 1973 February 24; 3 (Box 19–21)
      - Use copy for film reels 19-21, 1 (Box 19U)
  - 1973-1974
    - Pennsylvania, 1974 February 8; 3 (Box 22–24)
      - Use copy for film reels 22-24, 1 (Box 22U)
    - Princeton, 1974 February 9; 3 (Box 25–27)
    - Cornell, 1974 February 15; 3 (Box 28–30)
    - Columbia, 1974 February 16; 3 (Box 31–33)
    - Harvard, 1974 March 1; 3 (Box 34–36)
    - Dartmouth, 1973 March 2; 3 (Box 37–39)
  - 1974-1975
    - Cornell, 1975 January 10; 4 (Box 40–43)
    - Columbia, 1975 January 11; 4 (Box 44–47)
    - Columbia, 1975 January 31; 4 (Box 48–51)
    - Brown, 1975 January 25; 4 (Box 52–55)
    - Pennsylvania, 1975 February 1; 4 (Box 56–59)
      - Duplicating master, 6 computer files (DVD-Video)
      - Use copy for boxes 56-59, 1 (Box 56U)
      - Use copy for boxes 56-59, 1 (Box 56U2)
  - 1977
    - Columbia, 1977 February; film reel (16mm) (Box 60)
    - ECSC, 1977 March 5; film reel (16mm) (Box 61)
- Men's basketball game videotapes, 1957-2002; Accession 2006-A-029
  - UNC, 1957 March 12; videotape (VHS) (Box 1)
  - Cornell, 1963 February 15; videotape (VHS) (Box 2)
  - Harvard, 1968 February 3; videotape (VHS) (Box 3)
  - Harvard, 1968-1969; videotape (VHS) (Box 4)
  - Cornell, 1969 January 11; videotape (VHS) (Box 5)
  - Harvard, 1970 January 30; videotape (VHS) (Box 6)
  - Cornell, 1970 February 6; videotape (VHS) (Box 7)
  - Princeton, 1974-1975; videotape (VHS) (Box 8)
  - Princeton, 1975 January 31; videotape (VHS) (Box 9)
  - Harvard highlights, 1983 February 4; videotape (VHS) (Box 10)
    - Use copy, optical disk (DVD) (Box 10U)
  - Harvard, 1983 February 21-22; 2 (Box 471–472)
  - Dartmouth highlights, 1983 February 5; videotape (VHS) (Box 10)
    - Use copy, optical disk (DVD) (Box 10U)
  - Brown highlights, 1983 February 8; videotape (VHS) (Box 10)
    - Use copy, optical disk (DVD) (Box 10U)
  - Brown highlights, 1983 February 15; videotape (VHS) (Box 10)
    - Use copy, optical disk (DVD) (Box 10U)
  - UConn newslip, 1983; videotape (VHS) (Box 11)
    - Use copy, optical disk (DVD) (Box 11U)
  - Holy Cross, 1984 January 4; videotape (U-matic) (Box 12)
    - Use copy, videotape (VHS) (Box 12U)
  - UPenn, 1984 February 3; 2 (Box 507–508)
  - Brown, 1984 January 15; videotape (VHS) (Box 13)
  - Columbia, 1984 January 20; videotape (VHS) (Box 14)
  - Cornell, 1984 January 21; videotape (VHS) (Box 14)
  - Dartmouth, 1984 December 8; videotape (VHS) (Box 473)
  - Georgia, 1984-1985; videotape (VHS) (Box 15)
  - UConn, 1984-1985; videotape (VHS) (Box 16)
  - Brown, 1985 January 26; videotape (VHS) (Box 17)
  - Columbia, 1985 February 1; videotape (VHS) (Box 18)
  - Cornell, 1985 February 2; videotape (VHS) (Box 19)
    - Use copy, videotape (VHS) (Box 19U)
  - Harvard, 1985 February 8; videotape (VHS) (Box 21)
  - Dartmouth, 1985 February 9; videotape (VHS) (Box 22)
  - Princeton, 1985 February 15; videotape (VHS) (Box 23)
  - Cornell, 1985 February 22; videotape (VHS) (Box 24)
  - Columbia, 1985 February 23; videotape (VHS) (Box 25)
  - Princeton, 1985 March 2; videotape (VHS) (Box 26)
  - Harvard, 1985 March 9; videotape (VHS) (Box 27)
  - UConn, 1985 November 26; videotape (VHS) (Box 28)
  - Fairfield, 1985 November 30; videotape (VHS) (Box 29)
  - Holy Cross, 1986 January 7; videotape (VHS) (Box 30)
  - Brown, 1986 January 13; videotape (VHS) (Box 31)
  - Cornell, 1986 January 17; videotape (VHS) (Box 32)
  - Columbia, 1986 January 18; videotape (VHS) (Box 33)
  - Brown, 1986 January 25; videotape (VHS) (Box 34)
  - Princeton, 1986 February 7; videotape (VHS) (Box 35)
  - Penn, 1986 February 8; videotape (VHS) (Box 36)
  - Columbia, 1986 February 14; videotape (VHS) (Box 37)
  - Cornell, 1986 February 15; videotape (VHS) (Box 38)
  - Dartmouth, 1986 February 28; videotape (VHS) (Box 39)
  - Harvard, 1986 March 1; videotape (VHS) (Box 40)
  - UVM, 1986 November 29; videotape (VHS) (Box 41)
  - UMass, 1986 December 30; videotape (VHS) (Box 42)
  - Miami, 1986; videotape (VHS) (Box 43)
  - Notre Dame, 1986-1987; videotape (VHS) (Box 44)
  - Lafayette, 1986-1987; videotape (VHS) (Box 45)
  - Penn, 1986-1987; videotape (VHS) (Box 46)
    - Use copy, optical disk (DVD) (Box 46U)
  - Brown, 1987 January 10; videotape (VHS) (Box 47)
  - Cornell, 1987 January 16; videotape (VHS) (Box 48)
  - Columbia, 1987 January 17; videotape (VHS) (Box 49)
  - Fairfield, 1987 January 27; videotape (VHS) (Box 474)
    - Use copy (part 1), videotape (VHS) (Box 474UA)
    - Use copy (part 2), videotape (VHS) (Box 474UB)
  - Princeton, 1987 January 31; videotape (VHS) (Box 50)
  - Army, 1987 February 10; videotape (VHS) (Box 53)
  - Cornell, 1987 February 14; videotape (VHS) (Box 54)
  - Harvard, 1987 February 20; videotape (VHS) (Box 55)
  - Dartmouth, 1987 February 21; videotape (VHS) (Box 56)
  - Penn, 1987 February 28; videotape (VHS) (Box 57)
    - Use copy, optical disk (DVD) (Box 57U)
  - Holy Cross, 1987 December 9; videotape (VHS) (Box 512)
  - UTC, 1987 December 29; videotape (VHS) (Box 58)
  - Harvard, 1987; videotape (VHS) (Box 59)
  - Dartmouth, 1987; videotape (VHS) (Box 59)
  - UConn, 1987-1988; videotape (VHS) (Box 60)
  - Hofstra, 1988 January 3; videotape (VHS) (Box 61)
  - Bucknell, 1988 January 4; videotape (VHS) (Box 62)
  - B.U., 1988 January 5; videotape (VHS) (Box 63)
  - Army, 1988 January 6; videotape (VHS) (Box 64)
  - Manhattan, 1988 January 7 (Box 515)
  - Lehigh, 1988 January 9; videotape (VHS) (Box 65)
  - Fairfield, 1988 January 9; videotape (VHS) (Box 66)
  - Notre Dame, 1988 January 13; videotape (VHS) (Box 67)
  - Brown, 1988 January 16; videotape (VHS) (Box 68)
    - Use copy, videotape (VHS) (Box 68U)
  - Army, 1988 January 21; videotape (VHS) (Box 70)
  - Brown, 1988 January 23; videotape (VHS) (Box 71)
    - Use copy, videotape (VHS) (Box 71U)
  - Army, 1988 January 26; videotape (VHS) (Box 73)
  - Fairfield, 1988 February 9; videotape (VHS) (Box 73)
  - Penn, 1988 January 29; videotape (VHS) (Box 74)
  - Princeton, 1988 January 30; videotape (VHS) (Box 75)
  - Dartmouth, 1988 February 5; videotape (VHS) (Box 76)
    - Use copy, videotape (VHS) (Box 76U)
  - Harvard, 1988 February 6; videotape (VHS) (Box 77)
  - Columbia, 1988 February 12; videotape (VHS) (Box 78)
  - Cornell, 1988 February 13; videotape (VHS) (Box 79)
  - Princeton, 1988 February 19; videotape (VHS) (Box 80)
  - Princeton, 1988 February 19; videotape (VHS) (Box 81)
  - Cornell, 1988 February 26; videotape (VHS) (Box 82)
    - Use copy, videotape (VHS) (Box 82U)
  - Columbia, 1988 February 27; videotape (VHS) (Box 84)
    - Use copy, videotape (VHS) (Box 84U)
  - Harvard, 1988 March 4; videotape (VHS) (Box 86)
  - Dartmouth, 1988 March 5; videotape (VHS) (Box 475)
  - George Washington, 1988 November 26; videotape (VHS) (Box 87)
  - UConn, 1988 November 30; videotape (VHS) (Box 88)
  - Navy, 1988 December 2; videotape (VHS) (Box 89)
  - Providence, 1988 December 6; videotape (VHS) (Box 90)
  - Fordham, 1988 December 6; videotape (VHS) (Box 91)
  - FLU, 1988 December 28; videotape (VHS) (Box 92)
  - USC, 1988 February 29; videotape (VHS) (Box 93)
  - Hawaii, 1988-1989; videotape (VHS) (Box 94)
  - Fairfield, 1989 January 3; videotape (VHS) (Box 95)
  - Army, 1989 January 6; videotape (VHS) (Box 96)
  - Fairfield, 1989 January 10; videotape (VHS) (Box 97)
  - Brown, 1989 January 14; videotape (VHS) (Box 98)
  - Manhattan, 1989 January 17; videotape (VHS) (Box 99)
  - Brown, 1989 January 20; videotape (VHS) (Box 100)
  - Penn, 1989 January 27; videotape (VHS) (Box 100a)
    - Use copy, 1 (Box 100aU)
  - Princeton, 1989 January 28; videotape (VHS) (Box 101)
  - Cornell, 1989 February 3; videotape (VHS) (Box 102)
  - Columbia, 1989 February 4; videotape (VHS) (Box 103)
  - Harvard, 1989 February 10; videotape (VHS) (Box 104)
  - Dartmouth, 1989 February 11; videotape (VHS) (Box 105)
  - Harvard, 1989 February 25; videotape (VHS) (Box 106)
  - Cornell, 1989 March 4; videotape (VHS) (Box 107)
  - UConn, 1989 November 30; videotape (VHS) (Box 108)
    - Use copy, videotape (VHS) (Box 108U)
  - Case Western Reserve, 1989 December 1; videotape (VHS) (Box 110)
  - UMass, 1989 December 6; videotape (VHS) (Box 111)
  - Princeton, 1989-1990; videotape (VHS) (Box 112)
  - Florida International, 1989 December 28 (Box 514)
  - Brooklyn, 1990 January 4; videotape (VHS) (Box 113)
  - Fairfield, 1990 January 6; videotape (VHS) (Box 114)
  - Colgate, 1990 January 8; videotape (VHS) (Box 115)
  - Princeton, 1990 January 12; videotape (VHS) (Box 116)
    - Use copy (part 1), videotape (VHS) (Box 116UA)
    - Use copy (part 2), videotape (VHS) (Box 116UB)
  - Pennsylvania, 1990 January 13; videotape (VHS) (Box 476)
    - Use copy, optical disk (DVD) (Box 476U)
  - CCSU, 1990 January 17; videotape (VHS) (Box 117)
  - Brown, 1990 January 19; videotape (VHS) (Box 118)
  - Brown, 1990 January 26; videotape (VHS) (Box 119)
  - Brown, 1990 January 27; videotape (VHS) (Box 120)
  - Harvard, 1990 February 2; videotape (VHS) (Box 121)
    - Use copy, videotape (VHS) (Box 121UA)
  - Dartmouth, 1990 February 3; videotape (VHS) (Box 123)
    - Use copy, videotape (VHS) (Box 123UA)
  - Princeton, 1990 February 17; videotape (VHS) (Box 116)
    - Use copy, videotape (VHS) (Box 116UA)
  - Columbia, 1990 February 23; videotape (VHS) (Box 126)
  - Cornell, 1990 February 24; videotape (VHS) (Box 127)
  - Dartmouth, 1990 March 2; videotape (VHS) (Box 123)
    - Use copy, videotape (VHS) (Box 123UB)
  - Harvard, 1990 March 3; videotape (VHS) (Box 121)
    - Use copy, videotape (VHS) (Box 121UB)
  - St. Francis, 1990 November 8; videotape (VHS) (Box 130)
  - Norway, 1990 November 13; videotape (VHS) (Box 131)
  - St. Mary's, 1990 November 23; videotape (VHS) (Box 132)
  - Stanford, 1990 November 24; videotape (VHS) (Box 133)
    - Use copy, videotape (VHS) (Box 133U)
  - Hartford, 1990 November 27; videotape (VHS) (Box 135)
  - Navy, 1990 December 7; videotape (VHS) (Box 135)
  - UConn, 1990 November 29; videotape (VHS) (Box 136)
    - Use copy, videotape (VHS) (Box 136U)
  - Lehigh, 1990 December 1; videotape (VHS) (Box 138)
  - Fordham, 1990 December 5; videotape (VHS) (Box 138)
  - Bucknell, 1990 December 1; videotape (VHS) (Box 139)
  - Wagner, 1990 December 4; videotape (VHS) (Box 509)
  - Lafayette, 1990 December 7; videotape (VHS) (Box 140)
  - Fairleigh Dickinson, 1990 December 29; videotape (VHS) (Box 141)
  - Fairfield, 1991 January 3; videotape (VHS) (Box 142)
  - Colgate, 1991 January 5; videotape (VHS) (Box 143)
  - Princeton, 1991 January 11; videotape (VHS) (Box 145)
    - Use copy, videotape (VHS) (Box 144U)
  - Princeton, 1991 February 16; videotape (VHS) (Box 145)
  - Penn, 1991 January 12; 2 (Box 146–147)
  - Brooklyn College, 1991 January 15; videotape (VHS) (Box 148)
  - Brooklyn, 1991 January 16; videotape (VHS) (Box 149)
    - Use copy, videotape (VHS) (Box 149U)
  - Brown, 1991 January 19; videotape (VHS) (Box 151)
  - Brown, 1991 January 26; videotape (VHS) (Box 151)
  - New Hampshire, 1991 January 22; videotape (VHS) (Box 152)
  - Brown, 1991 January 26; videotape (VHS) (Box 153)
  - Columbia, 1991 February 1; videotape (VHS) (Box 154)
  - Cornell, 1991 February 2; videotape (VHS) (Box 155)
  - Dartmouth, 1991 February 8; videotape (VHS) (Box 157)
    - Use copy, videotape (VHS) (Box 157UA)
  - Penn, 1991 February 15; videotape (VHS) (Box 477)
    - Use copy, optical disk (DVD) (Box 477U)
  - Dartmouth, 1991 February 23; videotape (VHS) (Box 157)
    - Use copy, videotape (VHS) (Box 157UB)
  - Harvard, 1991 February 9; videotape (VHS) (Box 158)
  - Princeton, 1991 February 16; videotape (VHS) (Box 159)
  - Harvard, 1991 February 22; videotape (VHS) (Box 160)
  - Cornell, 1991 March 1; videotape (VHS) (Box 162)
  - Columbia, 1991 March 2; videotape (VHS) (Box 163)
  - Brown, 1991 September 21; videotape (VHS) (Box 164)
  - Lafayette, 1991 September 28; videotape (VHS) (Box 165)
  - Colgate, 1991 October 12; videotape (VHS) (Box 166)
  - Cornell, 1991 November 9; videotape (VHS) (Box 167)
    - Use copy, videotape (VHS) (Box 167U)
  - Honved, 1991 November 12; videotape (VHS) (Box 169)